<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DocOps Method on DocOps</title>
    <link>https://docops.info/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DocOps Method on DocOps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://docops.info/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles</title>
      <link>https://docops.info/docs/principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docops.info/docs/principles/</guid>
      <description>When applying the DocOps Method this principles will serve as guardrails.
 Documentation has a dual purpose. Documentation part for humans also make sense even without execution part in place. Documentation is single source of truth. DocOps Systems are idempotent multiple executions will produce the same result. DocOps System can be implemented one-way or round-trip. A system that only generates documentation from code isn’t following the DocOps concept. A system that modifies or enriches the documentation is within DocOps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differentiation from other Concepts</title>
      <link>https://docops.info/docs/differentiation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docops.info/docs/differentiation/</guid>
      <description>DocOps as described on the internet prior 2018, 2019 as Documentation with Dev Tools and Mindset.
GitOps, ChatOps and DocOps What is the differentiation to other potential similar concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>https://docops.info/docs/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docops.info/docs/tools/</guid>
      <description>As with all xyzOps concepts tools are the mortar that make the bricks stick together. As of now there aren’t any tools that are specifically designed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Participate</title>
      <link>https://docops.info/docs/participate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docops.info/docs/participate/</guid>
      <description>Be part of the DocOps movement, as the concept and practice are still evolving there are many opportunities and possibilities to contribute and influence the direction. You don’t have to be a developer or alike to contribute. Everyone with a brain is welcome.
Contribution Ideas This is a short list of topic that are alway welcome and simple to accomplish.
 Promote the DocOps concept to your co-worker, friends, Blog posts and Social Media.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>